const questions = [
  {
    number: 1,
    question: "Which of the following items counters healing?",
    answers: [
      "Bramble Vest",
      "Sunfire Cape",
      "Rabadons Deathcap",
      "Chalice of Power",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Sunfire Cape",
    explanation: "Check out the item in the Item section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 2,
    question: "What is the maximum number of demons you can have on the board?",
    answers: ["Zero", "Three", "Fourteen", "Six"],
    correctAnswer: "Six",
    explanation: "Check out the trait in the Home section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 3,
    question: "Which of the following champions has 3 traits?",
    answers: ["Swain", "Elise", "Morgana", "Aatrox"],
    correctAnswer: "Swain",
    explanation: "Check out the champions in the Champion section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 4,
    question: "Which of the following items is built by 2 BF Swords?",
    answers: [
      "Bloodthirster",
      "Infinity Edge",
      "Deathblade",
      "Spear of Shojin",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Deathblade",
    explanation: "Check out the item in the Items section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 5,
    question:
      "Which of the following classes jumps in the backline at the beggining of the round?",
    answers: ["Sorcerer", "Blademaster", "Assassin", "Shapeshifter"],
    correctAnswer: "Assassin",
    explanation: "Check out the traits in the Home section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 6,
    question: "Which of the following origins takes reduced magic damage?",
    answers: ["Dragon", "Imperial", "Noble", "Exile"],
    correctAnswer: "Dragon",
    explanation: "Check out the traits in the Home section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 7,
    question:
      "Which of the following items' effect is enhanced if the unit it's placed on is a Dragon?",
    answers: [
      "Dragons Claw",
      "Warmogs Armor",
      "Edge of Night",
      "Spear of Shojin",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Dragons Claw",
    explanation: "Check out the items in the Items section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 8,
    question: "Which of the following traits is activated by a single unit?",
    answers: ["Yordle", "Guardian", "Glacial", "Exile"],
    correctAnswer: "Exile",
    explanation: "Check out the traits in the Home section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 9,
    question: "Which of the following traits is a valid frontline option?",
    answers: ["Brawler", "Sorcerer", "Blademaster", "Ranger"],
    correctAnswer: "Brawler",
    explanation: "Check out the traits in the Home section to learn more!",
  },
  {
    number: 10,
    question: "Which of the following items reduces damage tekn from critical strikes?",
    answers: [
      "Warmogs Armor",
      "Gargoyle Stoneplate",
      "Bramble Vest",
      "Locket of the Iron Solari",
    ],
    correctAnswer: "Bramble Vest",
    explanation: "Check out the item in the Item section to learn more!",
  },
];

export default questions;